<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>niu.artube.xyz</title>
	<atom:link href="/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Just another WordPress site</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 02:18:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0</generator>
	<item>
		<title>What are the most common materials used for door handles?</title>
		<link>/2022/08/03/11/</link>
					<comments>/2022/08/03/11/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 06:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=140</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ByadminJanuary 5, 2021 Buy Best Stuff What are the best door handles in 2022? With so many options available on the market today, there’s sure to be something perfect for every homeowner. So don’t wait any longer – start shopping &#8230; <a href="/2022/08/03/11/">Continued</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-text-align-center">By<a href="https://buybeststuff.com/">admin</a>January 5, 2021</p>



<div class="wp-container-3 wp-block-columns">
<div class="wp-container-1 wp-block-column" style="flex-basis:33.33%">
<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img width="430" height="340" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/1-11.png" alt="" class="wp-image-141" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/1-11.png 430w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/08/1-11-300x237.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 430px) 100vw, 430px" /></figure>
</div>



<div class="wp-container-2 wp-block-column" style="flex-basis:66.66%">
<h4 class="has-text-align-center">Buy Best Stuff</h4>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center">What are the best door handles in 2022?</h3>



<p class="has-text-align-center">With so many options available on the market today, there’s sure to be something perfect for every homeowner. So don’t wait any longer – start shopping for your perfect set of door handles today!</p>
</div>
</div>



<div class="wp-container-4 wp-block-buttons">
<div class="wp-block-button aligncenter has-custom-font-size" style="font-size:15px"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-background" href="/door-handles-shops/" style="border-radius:8px;background-color:#b56a29">Where to Buy</a></div>
</div>



<p>There are many different types of materials that door handles can be made out of. The most common are metal, wood, and plastic.</p>



<p>Metal&nbsp;<strong><a href="/" data-type="URL" data-id="/">door handles</a></strong>&nbsp;are often made out of brass, bronze, steel, or aluminum. They are very durable and can withstand a lot of use. However, they can also be quite heavy.</p>



<p>Wooden door handles are usually made out of oak, mahogany, or cherry wood. They are quite sturdy and look stylish in most settings. However, they may not be as durable as metal door handles.</p>



<p>Plastic door handles are typically made from ABS plastic. They are the lightest option and often the cheapest. They also tend to be the least durable option.</p>



<div class="wp-container-7 wp-block-columns">
<div class="wp-container-5 wp-block-column">
<h3>What are the benefits of using a door handle made from a common material?</h3>



<p>There are many benefits of using a door handle made from a common material. The first benefit is that it is affordable. A door handle made from a common material is less expensive than a door handle made from a rare or expensive material.</p>



<p>Another benefit is that it is durable. A door handle made from a common material can withstand everyday use and abuse, whereas a door handle made from a rare or expensive material may not be as durable. Additionally, a door handle made from a common material is easy to find and replace if it ever breaks or becomes damaged. Lastly, a door handle made from a common material is easy to clean and maintain.</p>
</div>



<div class="wp-container-6 wp-block-column">
<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="600" height="500" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/2-16.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-142" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/2-16.jpg 600w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/08/2-16-300x250.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></figure>
</div>
</div>



<h3>Are there any other options available for a door handle made from a common material?</h3>



<p>If you’re looking for a finish that will make your door handle stand out, chrome is the way to go. It’s reflective and shiny, and it will add a touch of luxury to your door. If you’re looking for something more understated, a matte black finish might be a good option. It’s modern and stylish, and it will look great with any décor.</p>



<p>There are a few other options for door handles that are made from common materials. One option is a door handle that is made from brass. Brass is a metal that is made up of copper and zinc, and it has a golden color. It is a strong material, and it is resistant to corrosion. Another option is a door handle that is made from aluminum. Aluminum is a metal that is made up of carbon and magnesium, and it has a silver color. It is also resistant to corrosion, and it is lightweight.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2022/08/03/11/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is the door handle finished by brushed or polished?</title>
		<link>/2022/08/03/10/</link>
					<comments>/2022/08/03/10/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 06:56:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=136</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ByadminJanuary 28, 2021 Buy Best Stuff What are the best door handles in 2022? With so many options available on the market today, there’s sure to be something perfect for every homeowner. So don’t wait any longer – start shopping &#8230; <a href="/2022/08/03/10/">Continued</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-text-align-center">By<a href="https://buybeststuff.com/">admin</a>January 28, 2021</p>



<div class="wp-container-10 wp-block-columns">
<div class="wp-container-8 wp-block-column" style="flex-basis:33.33%">
<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="430" height="340" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/1-10.png" alt="" class="wp-image-137" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/1-10.png 430w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/08/1-10-300x237.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 430px) 100vw, 430px" /></figure>
</div>



<div class="wp-container-9 wp-block-column" style="flex-basis:66.66%">
<h4 class="has-text-align-center">Buy Best Stuff</h4>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center">What are the best door handles in 2022?</h3>



<p class="has-text-align-center">With so many options available on the market today, there’s sure to be something perfect for every homeowner. So don’t wait any longer – start shopping for your perfect set of door handles today!</p>
</div>
</div>



<div class="wp-container-11 wp-block-buttons">
<div class="wp-block-button aligncenter has-custom-font-size" style="font-size:15px"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-background" href="/door-handles-shops/" style="border-radius:8px;background-color:#c37d33">Where to Buy</a></div>
</div>



<p>This is a question that often comes up when choosing between the two finishes. The truth is, it depends on the individual <strong><a href="/" data-type="URL" data-id="/">door handles</a></strong>.</p>



<p>Some door handles are only available in brushed or polished finishes. If you’re looking for a specific finish, then you’ll need to consult with the manufacturer to see if it’s available.</p>



<p>If the door handle isn’t available in a specific finish, then you can usually choose between brushed and polished finishes. In most cases, brushed finishes look a little more rustic while polished finishes look a bit more modern.</p>



<p>It’s ultimately up to the individual to decide which finish they prefer. Some people prefer the more traditional look of brushed door handles while others prefer the more modern look of polished door handles.</p>



<p>Do you know the difference between brushed and polished door handles? Many people don’t, but there is a big difference.</p>



<p>Brushed door handles are more matte, while polished door handles are more shiny. Polished door handles are also a bit smoother than brushed door handles.</p>



<p>Which one you choose depends on your personal preference. Some people prefer the look of brushed door handles, while others prefer the look of polished door handles.</p>



<p>Either way, both types of door handles look great and will add some style to your home.</p>



<h3>Where would you typically find brushed door handles?</h3>



<p>Brushed door handles can typically be found in a few different places, depending on the style or brand of the handle. Some brushed door handles are installed on the inside of the door, while others are on the outside. There are also variations that can be mounted either vertically or horizontally.</p>



<h3>Where would you typically find polished door handles?</h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="512" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/2-15.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-138" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/2-15.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/08/2-15-300x150.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/08/2-15-768x384.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Most people would say that polished door handles are typically found in places such as hotels, restaurants and other areas where the public have access. This is because it is important to have a polished look to give a good impression to customers or guests.</p>



<p>Some establishments may choose to have door handles that are not polished in order to save on cleaning costs, but this can often look neglected or unprofessional. Polished door handles can be easy to clean and maintain with a quick wipe down, so it is a good option for businesses that want to keep a tidy appearance.</p>



<p>In residential homes, polished door handles are not as common, but they can still be found in some houses. They are often used on the front door in order to make a good first impression on visitors. Some people also choose to have polished door handles in their bedrooms or bathrooms for a luxurious feel.</p>



<p>There are many different types of door handles available, so it is important to choose the right ones for your needs. Polished door handles can be a great option for businesses and homes alike, and they can add a touch of class and sophistication to any space.</p>



<h3>Which do you think looks better – brushed or polished door handles?</h3>



<p>Brushed door handles are a popular choice for those who want their home to look modern and sleek. They usually have a very smooth finish, with few visible brush strokes. Polished door handles, on the other hand, have a high shine that can really make your door stand out.</p>



<p>The downside to polished door handles is that they require more maintenance than brushed ones – you’ll need to polish them regularly to keep them looking their best. If you’re not keen on doing this yourself, you may need to hire a professional to do it for you.</p>



<p>Brushed door handles are less Maintenance-intensive – all you need to do is give them a quick wipe down every now and then to keep them looking good. This makes them a popular choice for busy people who don’t have time for regular polishing.</p>



<p>So, which do you think looks better – brushed or polished door handles?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2022/08/03/10/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What is the difference between a door handle and a door knob?</title>
		<link>/2022/08/03/9/</link>
					<comments>/2022/08/03/9/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 06:52:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=132</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ByadminFebruary 18, 2021 Buy Best Stuff What are the best door handles in 2022? With so many options available on the market today, there’s sure to be something perfect for every homeowner. So don’t wait any longer – start shopping &#8230; <a href="/2022/08/03/9/">Continued</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-text-align-center">By<a href="https://buybeststuff.com/">admin</a>February 18, 2021</p>



<div class="wp-container-14 wp-block-columns">
<div class="wp-container-12 wp-block-column" style="flex-basis:33.33%">
<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="430" height="340" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/1-9.png" alt="" class="wp-image-133" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/1-9.png 430w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/08/1-9-300x237.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 430px) 100vw, 430px" /></figure>
</div>



<div class="wp-container-13 wp-block-column" style="flex-basis:66.66%">
<h4 class="has-text-align-center">Buy Best Stuff</h4>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center">What are the best door handles in 2022?</h3>



<p class="has-text-align-center">With so many options available on the market today, there’s sure to be something perfect for every homeowner. So don’t wait any longer – start shopping for your perfect set of door handles today!</p>
</div>
</div>



<div class="wp-container-15 wp-block-buttons">
<div class="wp-block-button aligncenter has-custom-font-size" style="font-size:15px"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-background" href="/door-handles-shops/" style="border-radius:8px;background-color:#c37d33">Where to Buy</a></div>
</div>



<p>Do you know the difference between a door handle and a door knob? Most people don’t realize that there is a difference, but there is!</p>



<p>A door knob is mainly used for turning the knob to open or close the door. A door handle usually has a lever that you push down to open the door.</p>



<p><strong><a href="/" data-type="URL" data-id="/"><strong><a href="/" data-type="URL" data-id="/">door handles</a></strong></a></strong> are usually made out of brass or porcelain, while door handles are typically made out of metal or plastic.</p>



<p>Knobs are often found on older homes, while handles are more popular on newer homes. Some people prefer knobs because they are easier to grip, while others prefer handles because they are more ergonomic.</p>



<h3>Why is it important to use the correct type of door handle or knob for your door?</h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="512" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/2-14.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-134" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/2-14.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/08/2-14-300x150.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/08/2-14-768x384.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>There are a few reasons why it’s important to use the correct type of door handle or knob for your door. One reason is that improper installation of a door handle or knob can cause the latch mechanism to bind and prevent the door from opening or closing. Additionally, using the incorrect type of door handle or knob can damage the door or the surrounding wall.</p>



<p>One of the most important things to consider when selecting a door handle or knob is the weight of the door. A standard interior door typically weighs about 80 pounds, so it’s important to use a handle or knob that is designed to support that weight. A lever-type handle is ideal for a standard interior door, as it’s specifically designed to support more weight than a traditional doorknob.</p>



<p>It’s also important to use the correct type of handle or knob for your door’s configuration. For example, if you have a double-door configuration, you’ll need to use a pair of handles or knobs that are matched in size and style.</p>



<p>If you’re not sure which type of handle or knob is right for your door, consult with a professional contractor who can help you select the right hardware for your application.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2022/08/03/9/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What are some features of a good door handle?</title>
		<link>/2022/08/03/8/</link>
					<comments>/2022/08/03/8/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 06:50:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=128</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ByadminMarch 24, 2021 Buy Best Stuff What are the best door handles in 2022? With so many options available on the market today, there’s sure to be something perfect for every homeowner. So don’t wait any longer – start shopping &#8230; <a href="/2022/08/03/8/">Continued</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-text-align-center">By<a href="https://buybeststuff.com/">admin</a>March 24, 2021</p>



<div class="wp-container-18 wp-block-columns">
<div class="wp-container-16 wp-block-column" style="flex-basis:33.33%">
<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="430" height="340" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/1-8.png" alt="" class="wp-image-129" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/1-8.png 430w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/08/1-8-300x237.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 430px) 100vw, 430px" /></figure>
</div>



<div class="wp-container-17 wp-block-column" style="flex-basis:66.66%">
<h4 class="has-text-align-center">Buy Best Stuff</h4>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center">What are the best door handles in 2022?</h3>



<p class="has-text-align-center">With so many options available on the market today, there’s sure to be something perfect for every homeowner. So don’t wait any longer – start shopping for your perfect set of door handles today!</p>
</div>
</div>



<div class="wp-container-19 wp-block-buttons">
<div class="wp-block-button aligncenter has-custom-font-size" style="font-size:15px"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-background" href="/wp-admin/post.php?post=56&amp;action=edit" style="border-radius:8px;background-color:#c37d33">Where to Buy</a></div>
</div>



<p>When it comes to <strong><a href="/" data-type="URL" data-id="/">door handles</a></strong>, there are a few things you need to consider before making a purchase. Here are some features of a good door handle:</p>



<h3>Ease of use</h3>



<p>The door handle should be easy to use, with a smooth operation. It shouldn’t require a lot of force to open the door.</p>



<h3>Security</h3>



<p>The door handle should be sturdy and well-made, so it can’t be easily forced open. It should also be resistant to moisture and weathering.</p>



<h3>Aesthetics</h3>



<p>The door handle should be attractive and complement the style of your home. It should also be made from quality materials that will last for years.</p>



<div class="wp-container-22 wp-block-columns">
<div class="wp-container-20 wp-block-column">
<ul><li>The handle should be easy to grip. This is especially important if you have arthritis or another condition that makes gripping difficult.</li><li>The handle should be easy to operate. It should have a smooth action and be easy to open and close.</li><li>The handle should be well-constructed and sturdy. It should be able to withstand everyday use without breaking or becoming loose.</li><li>The handle should match the style of your door. It should look like it belongs there, not like an afterthought.</li><li>The handle should be affordable. It doesn’t need to be cheap, but it shouldn’t cost a fortune either.</li></ul>
</div>



<div class="wp-container-21 wp-block-column">
<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="600" height="500" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/2-13.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-130" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/2-13.jpg 600w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/08/2-13-300x250.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></figure>
</div>
</div>



<p>If you’re looking for a new door handle, these are some of the features you’ll want to look for. Make sure to take your time in choosing one and don’t rush into making a decision. A good door handle can make all the difference in the world when it comes to your comfort and convenience.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2022/08/03/8/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How do you choose the right door handle for your home?</title>
		<link>/2022/08/03/7/</link>
					<comments>/2022/08/03/7/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 06:39:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=123</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ByadminApril 5, 2021 Buy Best Stuff What are the best door handles in 2022? With so many options available on the market today, there’s sure to be something perfect for every homeowner. So don’t wait any longer – start shopping &#8230; <a href="/2022/08/03/7/">Continued</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-text-align-center">By<a href="https://buybeststuff.com/">admin</a>April 5, 2021</p>



<div class="wp-container-25 wp-block-columns">
<div class="wp-container-23 wp-block-column" style="flex-basis:33.33%">
<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="430" height="340" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/1-7.png" alt="" class="wp-image-124" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/1-7.png 430w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/08/1-7-300x237.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 430px) 100vw, 430px" /></figure>
</div>



<div class="wp-container-24 wp-block-column" style="flex-basis:66.66%">
<h4 class="has-text-align-center">Buy Best Stuff</h4>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center">What are the best door handles in 2022?</h3>



<p class="has-text-align-center">With so many options available on the market today, there’s sure to be something perfect for every homeowner. So don’t wait any longer – start shopping for your perfect set of door handles today!</p>
</div>
</div>



<div class="wp-container-26 wp-block-buttons">
<div class="wp-block-button aligncenter has-custom-font-size" style="font-size:15px"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-background" href="/door-handles-shops/" style="border-radius:8px;background-color:#c37d33">Where to Buy</a></div>
</div>



<p><strong><a href="/" data-type="URL" data-id="/">Door handles</a></strong> are an important part of your home. They can make a statement about your style, and they also need to be functional. When you’re choosing the right door handle for your home, there are a few things to consider.</p>



<div class="wp-container-29 wp-block-columns">
<div class="wp-container-27 wp-block-column">
<p>The first thing to think about is what type of door handle you want. There are a few different options:</p>



<ul><li>Knob handles: these are the most common type of door handle. They’re easy to use, and they come in a variety of styles.</li><li>Lever handles: Lever handles are becoming more popular because they’re easier to use than knob handles. They’re perfect for people with arthritis or other hand problems.</li><li>Pull handles: Pull handles are perfect if you want a modern look for your home. They’re also easy to use, and they work well on doors that open outwards.</li></ul>
</div>



<div class="wp-container-28 wp-block-column">
<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="600" height="500" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/2-12.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-125" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/2-12.jpg 600w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/08/2-12-300x250.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></figure>
</div>
</div>



<div class="wp-container-32 wp-block-columns">
<div class="wp-container-30 wp-block-column">
<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="600" height="500" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/3-4.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-126" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/3-4.jpg 600w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/08/3-4-300x250.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></figure>
</div>



<div class="wp-container-31 wp-block-column">
<p>The second thing to think about is the material the door handle is made from. You can choose between metal, wood, or plastic door handles. Each material has its own benefits:</p>



<ul><li>Metal door handles: Metal door handles are strong and durable. They come in a variety of finishes, so you can find the perfect one for your home.</li><li>Wooden door handles: Wooden door handles are beautiful and natural looking. They come in a variety of types of wood, so you can find the perfect one for your home.</li><li>Plastic door handles: Plastic door handles are affordable and durable. They come in a range of colours, so you can find the perfect one for your home.</li></ul>
</div>
</div>



<p>Finally, you need to decide what function your door handle will serve. Do you need a keyed or keyless entry? A privacy lock or passage lock? A deadbolt or latch? Once you know what function you need, you can choose the right type of door handle.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2022/08/03/7/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How do you fix a loose door handle?</title>
		<link>/2022/08/03/6/</link>
					<comments>/2022/08/03/6/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 06:35:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=118</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ByadminMay 3, 2021 Buy Best Stuff What are the best door handles in 2022? With so many options available on the market today, there’s sure to be something perfect for every homeowner. So don’t wait any longer – start shopping &#8230; <a href="/2022/08/03/6/">Continued</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-text-align-center">By<a href="https://buybeststuff.com/">admin</a>May 3, 2021</p>



<div class="wp-container-35 wp-block-columns">
<div class="wp-container-33 wp-block-column" style="flex-basis:33.33%">
<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="430" height="340" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/1-6.png" alt="" class="wp-image-119" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/1-6.png 430w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/08/1-6-300x237.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 430px) 100vw, 430px" /></figure>
</div>



<div class="wp-container-34 wp-block-column" style="flex-basis:66.66%">
<h4 class="has-text-align-center">Buy Best Stuff</h4>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center">What are the best door handles in 2022?</h3>



<p class="has-text-align-center">With so many options available on the market today, there’s sure to be something perfect for every homeowner. So don’t wait any longer – start shopping for your perfect set of door handles today!</p>
</div>
</div>



<div class="wp-container-36 wp-block-buttons">
<div class="wp-block-button aligncenter has-custom-font-size" style="font-size:15px"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-background" href="/wp-admin/post.php?post=56&amp;action=edit" style="border-radius:8px;background-color:#c37d33">Where to Buy</a></div>
</div>



<p>There are a few ways you can fix a loose door handle. The best way to fix the problem, depends on the severity of the issue and the tools you have available.</p>



<p>If the <strong><a href="/" data-type="URL" data-id="/">door handles</a></strong> is loose because the screws that hold it in place are loose, you can tighten them up with a screwdriver. If the screws are stripped, you may need to use a drill or a power tool to get them tight again.</p>



<p>If the door handle is loose because the connecting rod is loose, you can reattach it using a screwdriver or a drill. If the connector is broken, you will need to replace it.</p>



<p>If the door handle is loose because the door itself is moving, you can adjust the hinges using a screwdriver or a drill. Make sure that the screws are tight so that the door does not move around anymore.</p>



<div class="wp-container-39 wp-block-columns">
<div class="wp-container-37 wp-block-column">
<h3>How do you know if you door handle is loose?</h3>



<p>Do you ever open your front door and feel like the handle just doesn’t quite fit right in your hand? Or maybe it feels extra wobbly when you turn it? If so, your door handle might be loose.</p>



<p>There are a few ways to know for sure. One is to give the handle a good wiggle; if it moves more than an inch or so, then it’s definitely loose. Another way to tell is to check the screws that hold the handle in place. If they’re loose, that means the handle is too.</p>



<p>If your door handle is loose, there are a few things you can do to fix it. The easiest option is to tighten the screws that hold the handle in place. You can do this with a screwdriver, or if you’re feeling brave, you can try tightening them by hand.</p>



<p>If tightening the screws doesn’t work, you might need to replace the entire handle. This can be a little bit trickier, but it’s definitely doable if you have some basic handyman skills.</p>



<p>If your door handle is loose, don’t worry – there’s a fix for that!</p>
</div>



<div class="wp-container-38 wp-block-column">
<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="600" height="500" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/2-11.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-120" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/2-11.jpg 600w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/08/2-11-300x250.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></figure>
</div>
</div>



<div class="wp-container-42 wp-block-columns">
<div class="wp-container-40 wp-block-column">
<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="600" height="500" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/3-3.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-121" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/3-3.jpg 600w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/08/3-3-300x250.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></figure>
</div>



<div class="wp-container-41 wp-block-column">
<h3>Can you fix a door handle without screws?</h3>



<p>A door handle is a common household item that is used to open and close a door. Door handles can be installed on either the interior or exterior of a door. Door handles are attached to a door by screws. However, there are ways to fix a door handle without screws.</p>



<p>One way to fix a door handle without screws is by using adhesive tape. Adhesive tape can be used to attach a door handle to a door. Another way to fix a door handle without screws is by using wire. Wire can be used to attach a door handle to a door.</p>



<p>If adhesive tape or wire are not available, another way to fix a door handle without screws is by using duct tape. Duct tape can be used to attach a door handle to a door. However, duct tape should not be used as a permanent solution because it is not as durable as adhesive tape, wire, or screws.</p>
</div>
</div>



<h3>How do you tighten a door handle without screws?</h3>



<p>It’s a question that has plagued homeowners for years – how do you tighten a door handle without screws? The answer is actually quite simple, and can be done with nothing more than a few everyday items.</p>



<p>All you need is a rubber band, some pliers, and a screwdriver. Start by using the screwdriver to remove the screws from the door handle. Once they’re removed, slip the rubber band over the handle so that it’s resting around the metal shaft. Next, use the pliers to twist the band tightly around the shaft. Finally, replace the screws and tighten them down.</p>



<p>The rubber band will create enough friction to keep the handle tight without needing any screws. This method is perfect for when you’re unable to remove the screws or when they’re stripped beyond repair.</p>



<h3>What kind of screws do you need to fix a door handle?</h3>



<p>There are a few different types of screws that you might need to fix a door handle. The type of screw you need will depend on the door handle itself and the material it is made from.</p>



<p>If your door handle is made from metal, you will need screws that are designed to attach metal to metal. These screws usually have a slot or Phillips head, and they can be easily identified by their silver color.</p>



<p>If your door handle is made from plastic, you will need screws with a phillips head. These screws are usually available in black or white, and they are designed to attach plastic to plastic.</p>



<p>It is important to use the correct type of screw when fixing a door handle, as using the wrong type of screw can damage the door handle or the door itself.</p>



<p>If neither of those solutions work, you may need to replace the door handle. To do this, remove the screws from both sides of the door handle and remove it from the door. Then, install a new door handle using the same screws. Be sure to align it with the existing holes in the door so it’s in line with the other handles on your door.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2022/08/03/6/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Are some door handles more functional than others?</title>
		<link>/2022/08/03/5/</link>
					<comments>/2022/08/03/5/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 06:30:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=114</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ByadminMay 26, 2021 Buy Best Stuff What are the best door handles in 2022? With so many options available on the market today, there’s sure to be something perfect for every homeowner. So don’t wait any longer – start shopping &#8230; <a href="/2022/08/03/5/">Continued</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-text-align-center">By<a href="https://buybeststuff.com/">admin</a>May 26, 2021</p>



<div class="wp-container-45 wp-block-columns">
<div class="wp-container-43 wp-block-column" style="flex-basis:33.33%">
<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="430" height="340" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/1-5.png" alt="" class="wp-image-115" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/1-5.png 430w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/08/1-5-300x237.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 430px) 100vw, 430px" /></figure>
</div>



<div class="wp-container-44 wp-block-column" style="flex-basis:66.66%">
<h4 class="has-text-align-center">Buy Best Stuff</h4>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center">What are the best door handles in 2022?</h3>



<p class="has-text-align-center">With so many options available on the market today, there’s sure to be something perfect for every homeowner. So don’t wait any longer – start shopping for your perfect set of door handles today!</p>
</div>
</div>



<div class="wp-container-46 wp-block-buttons">
<div class="wp-block-button aligncenter has-custom-font-size" style="font-size:15px"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-background" href="/wp-admin/post.php?post=56&amp;action=edit" style="border-radius:8px;background-color:#c37d33">Where to Buy</a></div>
</div>



<p>Doorknobs and levers are two of the most common <strong><a href="/" data-type="URL" data-id="/">door handles</a></strong> designs, but which one is more functional? In this article, we will take a look at both designs and compare their functionality.</p>



<p>First, let’s take a look at doorknobs. Doorknobs are typically round or oval in shape and are attached to the door by a spindle. To open the door, you grasp the doorknob and twist it. Doorknobs come in a variety of styles, including traditional, Victorian, and craftsman.</p>



<p>Levers are typically rectangular or square in shape and are attached to the door by a shaft. To open the door, you grasp the lever and push down on it. Levers come in a variety of styles, including traditional, contemporary, and rustic.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="512" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/2-10.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-116" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/2-10.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/08/2-10-300x150.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/08/2-10-768x384.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>So, which is more functional: doorknobs or levers? The answer depends on your needs. Here are some of the pros and cons of each design:</p>



<div class="wp-container-49 wp-block-columns">
<div class="wp-container-47 wp-block-column">
<p>Pros of Doorknobs:</p>



<ul><li>Doorknobs are typically less expensive than levers.</li><li>Doorknobs are easier to use for people with arthritis or other hand problems.</li><li>Doorknobs can be used with one hand.</li><li>Doorknobs can be used with gloves on.</li><li>Doorknobs are less likely to get dirty than levers.</li><li>Doorknobs can be easier to use in dark rooms or when your hands are full.</li></ul>
</div>



<div class="wp-container-48 wp-block-column">
<p>Cons of Doorknobs:</p>



<ul><li>Doorknob handles can be difficult to grip for some people.</li><li>Doorknob handles can be slippery when wet.</li></ul>
</div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2022/08/03/5/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What is the history behind door handles?</title>
		<link>/2022/08/03/4/</link>
					<comments>/2022/08/03/4/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 06:22:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=109</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ByadminOctober 8, 2021 Buy Best Stuff What are the best door handles in 2022? With so many options available on the market today, there’s sure to be something perfect for every homeowner. So don’t wait any longer – start shopping &#8230; <a href="/2022/08/03/4/">Continued</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-text-align-center">By<a href="https://buybeststuff.com/">admin</a>October 8, 2021</p>



<div class="wp-container-52 wp-block-columns">
<div class="wp-container-50 wp-block-column" style="flex-basis:33.33%">
<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="430" height="340" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/1-4.png" alt="" class="wp-image-110" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/1-4.png 430w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/08/1-4-300x237.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 430px) 100vw, 430px" /></figure>
</div>



<div class="wp-container-51 wp-block-column" style="flex-basis:66.66%">
<h4 class="has-text-align-center">Buy Best Stuff</h4>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center">What are the best door handles in 2022?</h3>



<p class="has-text-align-center">With so many options available on the market today, there’s sure to be something perfect for every homeowner. So don’t wait any longer – start shopping for your perfect set of door handles today!</p>
</div>
</div>



<div class="wp-container-53 wp-block-buttons">
<div class="wp-block-button aligncenter has-custom-font-size" style="font-size:15px"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-background" href="/wp-admin/post.php?post=56&amp;action=edit" style="border-radius:8px;background-color:#c37d33">Where to Buy</a></div>
</div>



<p>The door handle has been in use for centuries, with many different designs and shapes. But where did this simple invention come from and why do we use them?</p>



<p>The first <strong><a href="/door-handles-shops/" data-type="URL" data-id="/door-handles-shops/">door handles</a></strong> were likely made out of wood or metal, and were used to open doors manually. Over time, different designs were developed, including the lever-style handle which is still popular today.</p>



<p>There is no one definitive answer as to why door handles are used, but there are a few theories. Some believe that they were invented as a way to prevent draughts from entering a room, while others think that they were originally used as a way to protect the hands from heat or cold.</p>



<p>Whatever the reason, it’s clear that door handles have become an essential part of our lives. They provide a convenient way to open doors and make our homes more comfortable and secure.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote has-text-align-center"><p>Who invented the door handle and when?</p><cite>THE DOOR HANDLE, ALSO KNOWN AS A DOOR KNOB, WAS INVENTED BY THE ANCIENT EGYPTIANS. IT IS SAID THAT THE FIRST DOOR HANDLES WERE MADE FROM WOOD AND WERE USED TO OPEN TEMPLE DOORS.</cite></blockquote>



<h2>How have door handles evolved over time?</h2>



<div class="wp-container-56 wp-block-columns">
<div class="wp-container-54 wp-block-column">
<p>The design of door handles has evolved over time to meet the needs of the people using them. Originally, door handles were simple hooks that were used to manually open doors. Over time, lever-style handles were introduced to make it easier to open doors. These levers could be easily operated with one hand, which was important since people were often carrying items in their other hand.</p>



<p>More recently, electronic door handles have been introduced. These door handles are operated with a keypad or a touch screen, and they can be used to unlock doors remotely. This is useful for businesses that want to restrict access to certain areas or for people who want to be able to unlock their door from anywhere in the world.</p>



<p>Each type of door handle has its own advantages and disadvantages. Lever-style door handles are easy to use, but they can be difficult to operate if your hands are full. Electronic door handles are more secure than other types of door handles, but they can be expensive and they may require batteries or an electrical outlet.</p>



<p>Ultimately, the type of door handle that you choose depends on your specific needs and preferences. If you are looking for a simple, easy-to-use door handle, then a lever-style handle is probably the best option. If you need a more secure door handle or if you want to be able to unlock your door from anywhere in the world, then an electronic door handle is a good choice.</p>
</div>



<div class="wp-container-55 wp-block-column">
<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="600" height="800" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/2-9.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-112" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/2-9.jpg 600w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/08/2-9-225x300.jpg 225w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></figure>
</div>
</div>



<p>As time passed, people began to realize that it was much easier to open a door if there was a specific place to put their hand. This is when door handles began to be made out of metal. Metal was easier to grip than wood and it could also be used to lock and unlock doors.</p>



<p>Today, door handles come in all shapes and sizes. There are different types of handle for different types of doors. Some door handles are even made out of glass or plastic. No matter what type of door handle you have, it is important to know how to use it properly.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2022/08/03/4/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How important are door handles in the overall design of a room or building?</title>
		<link>/2022/08/03/3/</link>
					<comments>/2022/08/03/3/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 06:15:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=105</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ByadminOctober 29, 2021 Buy Best Stuff What are the best door handles in 2022? With so many options available on the market today, there’s sure to be something perfect for every homeowner. So don’t wait any longer – start shopping &#8230; <a href="/2022/08/03/3/">Continued</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-text-align-center">By<a href="https://buybeststuff.com/">admin</a>October 29, 2021</p>



<div class="wp-container-59 wp-block-columns">
<div class="wp-container-57 wp-block-column" style="flex-basis:33.33%">
<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="430" height="340" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/1-3.png" alt="" class="wp-image-106" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/1-3.png 430w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/08/1-3-300x237.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 430px) 100vw, 430px" /></figure>
</div>



<div class="wp-container-58 wp-block-column" style="flex-basis:66.66%">
<h4 class="has-text-align-center">Buy Best Stuff</h4>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center">What are the best door handles in 2022?</h3>



<p class="has-text-align-center">With so many options available on the market today, there’s sure to be something perfect for every homeowner. So don’t wait any longer – start shopping for your perfect set of door handles today!</p>
</div>
</div>



<div class="wp-container-60 wp-block-buttons">
<div class="wp-block-button aligncenter has-custom-font-size" style="font-size:15px"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-background" href="/wp-admin/post.php?post=56&amp;action=edit" style="border-radius:8px;background-color:#c37d33">Where to Buy</a></div>
</div>



<p><strong><a href="/door-handles-shops/" data-type="URL" data-id="/door-handles-shops/">Door handles</a></strong> are one of the most important aspects of a room or building. They are one of the first things that people see when they interact with a room or building, so it is important to make sure that they are aesthetically pleasing and functional.</p>



<p>There are a few things to consider when choosing door handles for a room or building. First, it is important to choose a style that matches the overall design aesthetic of the room or building. Second, it is important to choose a type of handle that is easy to use and fits the needs of the users. Lastly, it is important to choose a color and material that matches the other finishes in the room or building.</p>



<p>There are many different types of door handles available on the market, so it is important to do some research before making a purchase. Some popular types of door handles include:</p>



<ul><li>Knob handles: Knob handles are one of the most popular types of door handles because they are simple, easy to use, and affordable. They are typically made from plastic or metal and come in a variety of colors.</li><li>Lever handles: Lever handles are more expensive than knob handles, but they are easier to use for people with arthritis or other hand problems. They are typically made from metal and come in a variety of finishes.</li></ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="512" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/2-7.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-107" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/2-7.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/08/2-7-300x150.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/08/2-7-768x384.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>It is important to choose the right type of door handle for your needs. If you need a handle that is easy to use, then lever handles or towel bars are good options. If you need a handle that is more decorative, then knob handles or carved door knobs are good options.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p>Doors are generally opened and closed with a door handle. It’s actually pretty ingenious.</p></blockquote>



<p>The door handle is attached to a spindle that is connected to the doorknob. When you turn the door handle, it rotates the spindle, which in turn moves the doorknob. This mechanism allows you to open and close the door without having to touch the doorknob itself.</p>



<p>There are a few different types of door handles, but most of them work in basically the same way. some door handles have a thumb latch that you can press to lock or unlock the door. Others have a keyhole that you can use to unlock the door with a key.</p>



<p>Whatever type of door handle you have, it’s important to know how to use it properly. Make sure you read the instructions carefully before using your new door handle. And always be careful when opening and closing doors, especially if there are children or pets around.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2022/08/03/3/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What are the different types of door handles?</title>
		<link>/2022/08/03/2/</link>
					<comments>/2022/08/03/2/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 06:06:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=101</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ByadminNovember 26, 2021 Buy Best Stuff What are the best door handles in 2022? With so many options available on the market today, there’s sure to be something perfect for every homeowner. So don’t wait any longer – start shopping &#8230; <a href="/2022/08/03/2/">Continued</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-text-align-center">By<a href="https://buybeststuff.com/">admin</a>November 26, 2021</p>



<div class="wp-container-63 wp-block-columns">
<div class="wp-container-61 wp-block-column" style="flex-basis:33.33%">
<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="430" height="340" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/1-2.png" alt="" class="wp-image-102" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/1-2.png 430w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/08/1-2-300x237.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 430px) 100vw, 430px" /></figure>
</div>



<div class="wp-container-62 wp-block-column" style="flex-basis:66.66%">
<h4 class="has-text-align-center">Buy Best Stuff</h4>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center">What are the best door handles in 2022?</h3>



<p class="has-text-align-center">With so many options available on the market today, there’s sure to be something perfect for every homeowner. So don’t wait any longer – start shopping for your perfect set of door handles today!</p>
</div>
</div>



<div class="wp-container-64 wp-block-buttons">
<div class="wp-block-button aligncenter has-custom-font-size" style="font-size:15px"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-background" href="/wp-admin/post.php?post=56&amp;action=edit" style="border-radius:8px;background-color:#c37d33">Where to Buy</a></div>
</div>



<p><strong><a href="/door-handles-shops/" data-type="URL" data-id="/door-handles-shops/">Door handles</a></strong> come in a variety of shapes and sizes and can be made from a variety of materials. There are many different types of door handles available on the market, but some of the most common ones are listed below.</p>



<ul><li><strong>Knob-style handles</strong>– A knob-style handle is a round, ball-shaped handle that is attached to the door. The user grabs the knob and twists it in order to open the door.</li><li><strong>Lever-style handles</strong>– A lever-style handle is a long, thin handle that is attached to the door. The user grabs the lever and pulls or pushes it in order to open the door.</li><li><strong>Towel bar style handles</strong>– A towel bar style handle is a horizontal bar that is attached to the door. The user grabs either end of the bar in order to open the door.</li><li><strong>Pull handles</strong>– A pull handle is a horizontal or vertical bar that is attached to the door. The user grabs the handle and pulls on it in order to open the door.</li><li><strong>Push plates</strong>– A push plate is a flat metal or plastic plate that is attached to the door. The user pushes on the plate in order to open the door.</li><li><strong>Window cranks</strong>– Window cranks are round, ball-shaped handles that are used to open windows instead of doors.</li><li><strong>T-bar handles</strong>&nbsp;are often used on office doors, as they provide a sturdy grip.</li><li><strong>Cylinder handles</strong>&nbsp;can be locked or unlocked with a key, making them perfect for entry doors.</li></ul>



<p>All door handles have one thing in common – they allow people to open and close doors. However, the different types of door handle offer different benefits, so it is important to choose the right one for your needs. If you aren’t sure which type of door handle is right for you, consult a professional before making a purchase.</p>



<h3>Does the style of a door handle matter?</h3>



<div class="wp-container-67 wp-block-columns">
<div class="wp-container-65 wp-block-column">
<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="600" height="700" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/2-6.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-103" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/2-6.jpg 600w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/08/2-6-257x300.jpg 257w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></figure>
</div>



<div class="wp-container-66 wp-block-column">
<p>For many people, the style of a door handle is not something that they give much thought to. After all, it is just a utilitarian object that is used to open and closea door, right? Wrong! The style of a door handle can definitely matter, especially if you are looking to add some extra style and personality to your home.</p>



<p>There are many different types of door handles available on the market today, from traditional round knobs to sleek modern designs. It’s important to choose a handle that best suits your personal taste and style. If you are looking for a classic look, then a traditional round knob is a good option. If you are after a more contemporary vibe, then opt for a modern design with clean lines.</p>



<p>It’s also important to consider the material of the door handle. Metal handles are typically more durable than plastic handles, but they can also be prone to rusting over time. If you are looking for a long-lasting handle that will withstand the test of time, then metal is the way to go. Plastic handles are less durable but they are typically cheaper and easier to clean.</p>



<p>So, does the style of a door handle matter? The answer is definitely yes – it can make a big difference in the overall look and feel of your home. Choose the right handle for your needs and you will be sure to love it for years to come!</p>
</div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2022/08/03/2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
